You can now use Claude Code to edit your entire Shopify store.
You just ask it what you want and a few minutes later,
it updates your store exactly the way you asked.
You don't need any coding knowledge.
You don't need to add any apps.
You don't even need a developer.
You just need a single prompt.
Let me show what I mean. But have a look at this store here.
This is built on the standard horizon theme.
It's a standard horizon template.
And if you look down, it looks okay,
but it looks like every other store.
This is one that I edited with Claude code.
Now it looks night and day.
It looks so much better. It's gonna convert a lot better.
It has so much more detail
and it only took me about 30 minutes to build.
Honestly, in the last 15 years of scaling e commerce stores,
I've never seen anything like this.
For the first time ever, non technical founders
are going to have complete control over their store.
In this tutorial,
I'm going to show you how to set up a Claude code for Shopify
from start to finish. So grab yourself a coffee and let's get started.